Asada-sensei, your dick is hard... and shaking. null,pt]
Thats because Eri-sensei and Nijou-sensei are sucking it
Okay do not resist
You are the future of our school.
Make me wetter with your dick. null,pt]
If you suck hard like that, null,pt]
No you can not!
Sensei, you should appreciate us more.
Paint the walls of my pussy in white.
Thats right, really, really strong. null,pt]
Do not hold back. null,pt]
Do you listen to the noises in my pussy? null,pt]
O Meikoku should not take long.
Nijou-sensei, what is this Meikoku guy?
I really do not know. null,pt]
But we think its something that might be able to save and school
And this is our last hope!
But, why, this, with a simple teacher like me?
No, I think youre the perfect receptacle for Meikoku null,pt]
But for that, you must reach for nirvana. null,pt]
In the same way, 1 Is ejaculandu inside a woman- / null,pt]